{
    "subject": "resource/Gary_Wilhelms",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1931_births",
    "human_readable": "Gary Wilhelms is a subject of births in 1931.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9076045751571655,
            "question": "Is there information about Gary Wilhelms' life before 1931?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8228106498718262,
            "question": "When was Gary Wilhelms born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7825643420219421,
            "question": "What significant events might have happened in the year of Gary Wilhelms' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7423320412635803,
            "question": "What year marks Gary Wilhelms' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6856674551963806,
            "question": "What historical context existed during Gary Wilhelms' birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.662158191204071,
            "question": "Is there information available about Gary Wilhelms' family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6058580875396729,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about significant events happening in the world during Gary Wilhelms' birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5977280139923096,
            "question": "Were there any notable births or deaths in the same year as Gary Wilhelms?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5478107929229736,
            "question": "Can you find any details about Gary Wilhelms' childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29336094856262207,
            "question": "In what year did Gary Wilhelms enter the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gary Wilhelms is a subject of births in 1931.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1757_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any details about Gary Wilhelms' childhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1757_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable births or deaths in the same year as Gary Wilhelms?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1757_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about significant events happening in the world during Gary Wilhelms' birth year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1757_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1757_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents do not provide any information about Gary Wilhelms' birth year, except for his age (71 years) and birth date (January 12, 1952). This suggests that his birth year is 1952, not 1931."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information that supports the statement \"Gary Wilhelms is a subject of births in 1931.\" According to the available data, Gary's birth date is given as January 12, 1952."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}